Lloyd E. Cotsen collection of Potter Family photographs,1865-1935: Finding Aid
Cotsen Children's Library
- Landscapes, 1880 May-1913 September; 1021 items
  - Bassenthwaite, 1906 September 6; 730; 1 item 11.4 x 15.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 6 1906 / Bassenthwaite / B / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 729.
  - Bassenthwaite, 1906 September 6; 731; 1 item 11.3 x 15.5 cm.
  - Bassenthwaite, 1906 September 6; 732; 1 item 11.4 x 15.6 cm.
  - Borrowdale, 1906 September 22; 733; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 22 1906 / Borrowdale / B / R Potter.
  - Field of ferns, Borrowdale, 1906 September 22; 734; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 22 1906 / Borrowdale / B / R Potter.
  - Field of ferns, Borrowdale, 1906 September 22; 735; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
  - Grange-on-Borrowdale, 1906 August; 736; 1 item 7.4 x 9.6 cm.
  - Portinscale, 1906 September; 737; 1 item 7.3 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 1906 / Portinscale / Sp / R Potter.
  - Grange-on-Borrowdale, 1906 September; 738; 1 item 7.2 x 9.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1906 / Grange / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 739.
  - Grange-on-Borrowdale, 1906 September; 739; 1 item 7.2 x 9.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1906 / Sep. / Grange / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 738.
  - Grange-on-Borrowdale, 1906; 740; 1 item 7.3 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1906 / Grange / R Potter.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1906 September; 741; 1 item 11.3 x 15.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep.1906 / Lingholm / B / R Potter.
  - Lingholm grounds, haystacks, 1906 September; 742; 1 item 11.3 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep.1906 / Lingholm / B / R Potter / v.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1906 September; 743; 1 item 11.4 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep.1906 / B / R Potter / v.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1906 September; 744; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep.1906 / Lingholm / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1906 September; 745; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep.1906 / Derwent Water / B / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1906 September; 746; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1906 September; 747; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1906 September; 748; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm 1906 / 11 1/2 B Wd.
  - Lingholm house from the shore of Derwentwater, 1906 September; 749; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1906 / Lingholm / B / R Potter.
  - Shore of Derwentwater, 1906 September; 750; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1906 / B / Derwent Water / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1906 September; 751; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1906 / Derwent Bay / B / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1906 September; 752; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1906 / Derwent Bay / B / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 753.
  - Derwent Bay, 1906 September; 753; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1906 / Derwent Bay / B / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 752.
  - Derwentwater, 1906 September; 754; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 23; 755; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 23 Jul 1907 / B / R Potter 11 1/2.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 27; 756; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / July 27 1907 / B 11 1/2 w d / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 757.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 27; 757; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / July 27 1907 / B 11 1/2 w d / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 756.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 30; 758; 1 item 16.3 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / July 30 1907 / B 11 1/2 w d / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 759-760.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 30; 759; 1 item 16.3 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / July 30 1907 / B 11 1/2 w d / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 758, 760.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 30; 760; 1 item 16.3 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 758-759.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 30; 761; 1 item 16.3 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / July 30 1907 / B 11 1/2 w d / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 762.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 30; 762; 1 item 16.3 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 761.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 31; 763; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 31 1907 / Imp. O (1) / 11 1/2 wd / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 764.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July 31; 764; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 31 1907 / Imp. O (1) / Lingholm / 11 1/2 wd / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 763.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July; 765; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / Sp. / 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July; 766; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / B / R Potter.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July; 767; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / w [?]w [illegible] / R Potter.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1907 July; 768; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1907 / B / 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 July; 769; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1907 / July / B wd / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 August 5; 770; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 5 Aug 1907 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August 8; 771; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay.Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 8 Aug 1907 / Derwent Water from Lingholm / l3 1l B / R Potter.
  - Grange-on-Borrowdale, 1907 August 17; 772; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay.Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Grange Borrowdale / Aug 17 1907 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 23; 773; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay.Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 23 1907 / Imp O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Trees, Derwent Bay, 1907 August 23; 774; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 23 1907 / Imp O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater and Walla Crag from Lingholm, 1907 August 24; 775; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Walla Crag / Aug 24 1907 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 August 29; 776; 1 item 11.3 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Aug 29 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 777.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 August 29; 777; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Aug 29 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 776.
  - Derwent Isle, Derwentwater, 1907 August 29; 778; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Marshalls Island / Aug 29. 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Marshalls Island now known as Derwent Isle.
  - Fawe Park from Lingholm, 1907 August 29; 779; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Fawe Park / Aug 29. 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Boat pulled up under trees on bank of Derwentwater, 1907 August 29; 780; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 29. 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August 29; 781; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water from Lingholm / Aug 29. 1907 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater?, 1907 August 30; 782; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 30. 1907 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater.
  - Derwentwater?, 1907 August 30; 783; 1 item 8.2 x 10.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 30. 1907 / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 30; 784; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 30. 1907 / Imp. O. 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 30; 785; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 30. 1907 / Imp. O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 786-787.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 30; 786; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 30. 1907/ Derwent Bay / Imp. O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 785, 787.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 30; 787; 1 item 16.4 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 30. 1907/ Imp. O. / 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 785-786, trimmed down. Corner folded.
  - Derwent Bay, 1907 August 30; 788; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 30. 1907/ B 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Fawe Park and Derwentwater, 1907 August 30; 789; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / Aug 30. 1907/ S.p. / 11 1/2 / R Potter. House visible through trees left of center is Fawe Park.
  - Derwentwater, Roseliers?, 1907 August 30; 790; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Roseliers / Aug 30. 1907/ Sp. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 791. Forms a near panorama with CTSN Potter 789, depicting Fawe Park. Rupert Potter's inscription appears to name the estate visible through trees at right-hand side of image, but is difficult to read.
  - Derwentwater, Roseliers?, 1907 August 30; 791; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: [Roseliers] / Aug 30. 1907/ Sp. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 790. Forms a near panorama with CTSN Potter 789, depicting Fawe Park. Rupert Potter's inscription appears to name the estate visible through trees at right-hand side of image, but is difficult to read.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 August 30; 792; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Aug 30 1907 / Imp.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 300. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 793.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 August 30; 793; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Aug 30 1907 / Imp.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 300. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 792.
  - Derwentwater and Walla Crag from Lingholm, 1907 August; 794; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Walla Crag / Aug 1907 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: O22.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 795; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. wd / 11 1/2 R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: [5]0. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 796-797.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 796; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. / wd / 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: [?]0. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 795, 797.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 797; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. 11 1/2 / w.d / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: [?]0. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 795-796.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 798; 1 item 11.1 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 799.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 799; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Walla Crag / Derwentwater. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 798.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 800; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Imp O. / 11 1/2 wd / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1907 August; 801; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1907 / Derwent Water / Imp O. 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, through the trees, 1907 September 3; 802; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / 3 Sep 1907 / I. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Shore of Derwentwater, Lingholm, 1907 September 3; 803; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / Sep 3 1907 / I. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Shore of Derwentwater, Lingholm, 1907 September 3; 804; 1 item 16.4 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / Sep 3 1907 / I. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 805.
  - Shore of Derwentwater, Lingholm, 1907 September 3; 805; 1 item 16.4 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / Sep 3 1907 / I. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 804.
  - Shore of Derwentwater, Lingholm, 1907 September 3; 806; 1 item 16.4 x 12.0 cm.
  - Derwentwater and Walla Crag, 1907 September 6; 807; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwentwater / Sep 6. 1907 / I. O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 808.
  - Derwentwater and Walla Crag, 1907 September 6; 808; 1 item 11.9 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1907 / [Imp. Orth.] / Derwent Water / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 807.
  - Derwentwater and Lodore Falls Hotel, 1907 September 6; 809; 1 item 11.9 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Sep 6 1907 / [I. O] 11 1/2 / Derwent Water / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 810.
  - Derwentwater and Lodore Falls Hotel, 1907 September 6; 810; 1 item 11.9 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1907 [Imp. Or] / Derwent Water / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 809.
  - Derwentwater, 1907 September 6; 811; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Sep 6 1907 / [I. O] 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Lingholm from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 812; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay.Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm from Swinside / Sep 7 1907 / [Imp. O] / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 07. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 813.
  - Lingholm from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 813; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 07. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 812.
  - Lingholm from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 814; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm from Swinside / Sep. 7 1907 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Cat Bells from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 815; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Cat Bells from Swinside / Sep. 7 1907 / R Potter / Imp. O.
  - Walla Crag from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 816; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Sep 7. 1907 / Imp. O / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 817; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water from Swinside / Sep 7. 1907 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 818.
  - Derwentwater from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 818; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water from Swinside / Sep 7. 1907 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 817.
  - Skiddaw from Swinside, 1907 September 7; 819; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Skiddaw from Swinside / Sep 7. 1907 / Imp.O. / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 07.
  - Abbot's Bay, Derwentwater, 1907 September 16; 820; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1907 / Sep 16 / Imp.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 016.
  - Abbot's Bay, Derwentwater, and High Seat, 1907 September 16; 821; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
  - View from foot of Cat Bells toward Grange, 1907 September 16; 822; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
  - Great Bay, Derwentwater, and Lodore Falls Hotel, 1907 September 16; 823; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1907 / Sep 16 / Imp.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: 0?.
  - Newlands Valley with low clouds, 1907 September 18; 824; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Newlands / Imp O. 11 1/2 / Sep 18 1907 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 825.
  - Newlands Valley with low clouds, 1907 September 18; 825; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Newlands / Imp O. / Sep. 1907 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 824.
  - Newlands Valley with low clouds, 1907 September 18; 826; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1907 / Sep 18 / Imp. O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Hedge of flowers, Newlands Valley, 1907 September 18; 827; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Newlands / Sep 18 190 / Imp. O. 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, from Derwent Isle?, 1907 September 19; 828; 1 item 11.1 x 13.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Lords Island visible to the right. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1907 / Sep. 19 [NTG] / SP / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 829.
  - Derwentwater, from Derwent Isle?, 1907 September 19; 829; 1 item 11.1 x 13.7 cm.